drivetime.com 2016-10-12

# Privacy Policy | DriveTime.com

#### Our Privacy Policy

The privacy of your information is important to us. We use security measures to safeguard all details of your DriveTime experience. We do collect and use information from your visit, though, so please read on for more details. 

At DriveTime, we believe that the confidentiality and protection of your personal information is one of our fundamental responsibilities. We use security measures to safeguard your information with us and want you to know that you can count on us to protect the privacy and security of your customer information.

While you can visit and browse through the DriveTime.com website without disclosing who you are or providing any other personal information about yourself, some key features of the site require us to collect information from our users. Learn more about our privacy policy below. **By using this site, you agree to the terms of this privacy policy. For other terms and conditions of using this site,[click here](https://www.drivetime.com/info/termsofuse)**.

#### Information Collection and Use

In general, you can visit DriveTime.com without telling us who you are or revealing personal information about yourself. We generally collect personally identifying information with your knowledge and consent, but our servers may automatically collect information about you, your device, or your online behavior, and we may have information about you from third party sites. 

We generally collect personally identifying information with your knowledge and consent. For example, when you use the website, a password, user ID, your name, telephone number, street or email address, and other personally identifying information may be requested or collected.

We also may use nonpublic, personal information about you that you or someone else has provided to us and that is not publicly available as well as information about your transactions with us. That information includes:

  * Information we receive from a consumer-reporting agency.
  * Your payment history if you have previously purchased or leased a vehicle from us.
  * Information we collect from you via the credit application page located at <https://www.drivetime.com/getapproved>.

Our servers may also automatically collect information about you, your online behavior and your computer, mobile, or other device. The information may include, without limitation, information about the device you are using, such as the make, model, settings, and specification of the device, and may also include the geographic location of you or your device, as well as the date/time stamp, IP address, pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, the site(s), application(s), destination(s), or service(s) you arrived from, and other clickstream data.

If you choose to access, visit or use any third party service(s), that may be integrated with or linked to DriveTime’s website, we may receive personally identifiable information and other information about you and your computer, mobile or other device that you have made available to those services, including information about your contacts on those services. Your decision to use third party service(s) in connection with DriveTime is voluntary. DriveTime does not operate the third party service(s) or links and is not responsible for the privacy protection or content outside of the DriveTime website. We reserve the right to use, sell, transfer, assign, share, and provide access to all personally identifying information and other information about you and your computer, mobile or other device that we receive through third-party social networking services in the same ways described in this Agreement as all of your other information.

#### Information Use

We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our customers or former customers to anyone, except as permitted by law. 

We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our customers or former customers to anyone, except as permitted by law.

We use personally identifiable information you supply to provide you with the content you have requested. We may also use the information to communicate with you about new features, products or services, or to improve the services that we offer by tailoring them to your needs.

We may share information about you, your computer, mobile or other device, with our parent, subsidiaries, and affiliates. We may also share information about you to unaffiliated parties so that we may conduct our business, and so we or the unaffiliated parties may offer you products and services. There are also times when you may provide information about yourself to us in areas that may be managed or participated in by third parties. In such cases, the information may be used by us and such third party(ies), each pursuant to its own policies. While we may seek to require such third parties to follow appropriate privacy policies and will not authorize them to use this information except for the express purpose for which it is provided, we are not responsible for any actions or policies of third parties.

We may, disclose certain information to government agencies, consumer-reporting agencies, and other outside parties as permitted or required by the Federal Privacy Act and other applicable laws, for example, to cooperate with governmental, law enforcement, or other investigation(s) or legal proceedings.

We reserve the right to use the information we collect about you, your computer, mobile or other device, including geographic information, which may at times be able to identify you, for any lawful business purpose, including without limitation, to help diagnose problems with our servers, to gather broad demographic information, analyze trends, track users’ movements around the website, and to otherwise administer the website.

We and our service providers use analytics to analyze traffic to this website in order to help us understand our customers’ and visitors’ needs and to continually improve our site. Some of the analytics use the tracking technologies described below. We reserve the right to use, sell, transfer, and share data about our users for any lawful business purpose.

#### Local Device Storage (“Cookies”) and Tracking Technologies

We may use local device storage or tracking technologies for any lawful business purpose, including to gather and/or store information, deliver content, and administer services on the website. 

A cookie is a small text file containing information that a website stores on your computer's hard disk so the site can remember something about you at a later time. Cookies can make a website more useful by allowing the site to personalize information for visitors and by storing information about user preferences on a particular site so that the user does not have to re-enter information, etc., each time he or she returns to the site. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major websites such as DriveTime.com use them to provide useful features for their customers.

We may use local device storage or tracking technologies, such as web beacons, web bugs, clear gifs, and similar technologies, for any lawful business purpose, including without limitation to determine which of our messages have been opened by recipients so we can gauge the effectiveness of marketing campaigns, to track usage patterns, the movements of individual users, and your geographic location, to help diagnose problems with our servers, to gather broad demographic information, to analyze trends, to conduct research, to deliver editorial content, to record registration and personalization information, and to otherwise administer services on the website. Local device storage may also collect and store your personally identifiable information, which may be shared with our parent, subsidiaries, affiliates, and other companies.

Most browsers are automatically set up to accept cookies. If you would prefer, you can set your browser to reject cookies. However, you might not be able to use certain features on the site. Other third parties may also use tracking technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this site and other sites you have visited, and for other lawful business purposes. The use of tracking technologies by third parties is subject to their own privacy policies, not this privacy policy, and we have no responsibility or liability in connection with the use of tracking technologies by third parties.

#### Transfer of Information

Your information may be transferred to and maintained on servers and database located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may by different and may not be as protective as your jurisdiction. We may transfer your information to and from any state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction, and process it in the United States or elsewhere. We may transfer any information we have about you in connection with a change in corporate control, including but not limited to a merger or sale (including transfers made as part of insolvency or bankruptcy proceedings) involving all or part of DriveTime or as part of a corporate reorganization or stock sale. Your consent to this privacy policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to any such transfer.

#### Information Security

This website secures your private information using a SSL Certificate, but because no data security system is impenetrable, we cannot guarantee the security of the information you provide, and you agree to assume that risk. 

This website secures your private information using a SSL Certificate. Information exchanged with any address beginning with “https” is encrypted using SSL before it is transmitted.

Because no data transmission is completely secure, and no system of physical or electronic security is impenetrable, however, we cannot guarantee the security of the information you send to us or the security of our servers, networks or databases, and by using the website you agree to assume all risk in connection with the information sent to us or collected by us when you access, visit or use the website, including without limitation your personally identifiable information or other information, and we are not responsible for any loss of such information or the consequences thereof.

If you elect to store information, such as your personally identifiable information or other information, where others may access it, we are not responsible for any loss of such information or the consequences thereof. If you lose a computer, mobile or other device, or it is stolen, that contains your personally identifiable information or other information, it is up to you to take all the steps necessary to protect yourself.

In the unlikely event that we believe the security of your information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you. If notification is appropriate, we may notify you via your computer, mobile or other device.

#### Kids and Parents

This website is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 13. No one under age 13 is allowed to register for the services provided on this website. Minors between ages 13 – 17, inclusive, must get the permission of their parent(s) or legal guardian(s) before making purchases, including subscriptions for services on this website. If your children disclose information about themselves in publicly accessible areas of the website, they may get unsolicited messages from other parties. Accordingly, you should tell them not to do so. If you are worried bot your children’s activities or their privacy on the website, we encourage you to contact our privacy Policy Coordinator as describe below.

#### Assistance to Victim of Identity Theft

If you suspect that someone has had unauthorized access to your account with us or access to your personally identifiable information, you should report this crime to your local law enforcement agency and to the Federal Trade Commission (FTC). To speak with a trained FTC telephone counselor, call toll-free 1-877-IDTheft ([1-877-438-4338](tel:18774384338)). Or, to enter information about your complaint into a secure FTC online database, visit [www.consumer.gov/idtheft](http://www.consumer.gov/idtheft). The site also provides links to consumer education materials. 

#### Notification of Changes

These practices and policies are subject to change, but we will communicate any material changes to you. The practices and policies in this disclosure replace all previous privacy notices or statements of DriveTime.

#### Contacting the Web Site and the Privacy Policy Coordinator

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, please contact:

Compliance Team, 1720 West Rio Salado Parkway, Tempe, AZ, 85281 or [privacy@drivetime.com](mailto:privacy@drivetime.com). Make sure to include enough information so that we can help you, such as your name, contact information, and the specific website mobile site, application, and/or other service you are contacting us about.

If you don’t agree to the terms contained in this privacy policy, you must immediately exit the website.

#### Downloadable Privacy Documents
